How have you changed? You came to the rally, they said
Как вы изменили вышли на митинг сказали
Kadyrov
Кадыров
the dog,
пёс
Hello, I greet you, you
Здравствуйте приветствую тебя вы имперец
are an imperial, I am a nationalist, o I am from the city of Khmelnitsky And
я националист о Я из города Хмельницкий
what city are you from? Moscow, that’s where you
А Вы из какого города Москва вот куда
will be, this is the city of Khmelnitsky. I say
будеть это же город Хмельницкий Я говорю
you, it turns out you are a Russian nationalist, yes, it turns out
вы получается вы русский националист да
this is the region. Well, hug me drunk Yes
получается это область Ну хмельни обни
A  you're drunk from Khmelnitsky itself
Да А вы хмельни из самого Хмельницкого
Yes, but I understand the city Ponya That is, you're like an
Да а города я понял Поня То есть вы типа
imperial,
имперец
yes I'm on your flag, it's
да я нали вот на вашем флаге Я его
just not the first time I've seen him there in the middle,
просто не первый раз вижу там в середине
some kind of horseman kills a dragon, that's who he is
какой-то этот конник дракона убивает это
What kind of prince is this
же кто такой Что за князь это это
George  Victorious And what is he there on the
Георгий Победоносец А что он там на
flag? Well, you understand, we are still the Heirs of the
флаге Ну понимаете мы вс-таки Наследники
Byzantine Empire, but I understand, you understand,
Византийской империи а понял понимаете
continuity exists. And when,
преемственность существует А когда вот
when did Russian nationalists
когда вот русские националисты
inherit the continuity of the
унаследовали преемственность
Byzantine Empire? In what year
Византийской империей В каком году
can you remind me? I taught history poorly,
можете Напомнить Я плохо историю учил
listen. Well, Russia became an empire back in the
слушайте Ну Россия стала империей ещё в
10th century.  as in the 10th century, the Russian Empire
X веке как в X веке Российская империя
povi in ​​1721 by decree of Peter I in the century
пови в 1721 году указом Петра I в веке
Yes, when it became the successor of
Да когда она стала преемником
Byzantium, plus or minus The whole process
Византии плюс-минус Весь процесс на
actually began when we accepted
самом деле начался когда мы приняли
Christianity So you accepted Christianity
христианство Так вы приняли христианство
Well, we accepted Christianity Russia accepted with you
Ну мы приняли христианство Русь приняли
We accepted with you  styles yes But
с Вами Мы с вами приняли стили да Но
like you were the periphery of the Byzantine
типа вы были периферией византийского
orthodox world The periphery
вот этого православного мира Периферия
we were not we were not The periphery was never like
мы не мы не были Периферия никогда как
Periphery Constantinople was yes that
Периферия Константинополь был да вот это
was right about and Moscow is crap in
был прямо о а Москва так это хрень
short so far, far from the entire
короче аж далеко-далеко от всего
Orthodox world Well listen Damn well you
православного мира Ну слушайте Блин ну
understand I  I understand what you are talking about
понимаете Я понимаю о чём вы говорите
simply
просто
When in what year and who transferred the
Когда в какой год и кто передал
succession of the Byzantine Empire to
преемственность Византийской империи
Moscow Well, you know, you can
Москве Ну понимаете Вы как бы можете
say different things, but
разные вещи говорить но тем не
nevertheless, Russia
менее Россия
adopted Christianity
это переняла христианство
in a good way, adopted it there, Serbia adopted it,
в хоро переняла там Сербия переняла
Greece adopted it, Why not Greece,
Греция переняла Почему не Греция
for example,
например
Greece adopted it earlier Yes  Well, because the
Греция раньше переняла Да ну потому что
Greeks apparently couldn’t find theirs.
греки видимо не смогли оть свою
I mean, the Greeks couldn’t. You understand
В смысле греки не смогли Ты понимаешь
now you’re saying, look. Dude, you who
сейчас говоришь смотри Чувак ты который
ran. In short, somewhere back in the
бегал Короче ещё когда-то где-то там в
woods like on Mamoto, however,
лесах типа на мамото тем тем не менее
who ran to Turkey, who ran back and forth
кто бегал на Турцию кто бегал туда-сюда
look again, I was running Greece there Serbia Bulgaria
смотри бегал Греция там Сербия Болгария
that's how many Orthodox countries there are, yes
вот сколько есть православных стран да С
Why would
чего бы
you
вы
Nigo that we are so
Ниго что мы такие
awesome
охуительные
we are just God's Chosen Chosen
мы просто Богом Избранная Избранная
country
страна
And I understand yes You see what with And in what
А понял да Видите в чём при А в каком
year God
году вас Бог
chose you chose us Well, we have always been
избрал нас избрал Ну всегда мы были
Orthodox  people not when you
православными людьми не когда вот вы
were there before idols in short va Well for
были раньше там идолы короче ва Ну для
me, look Russia has a thousand-year
меня смотри Россия имеет тысячелетнюю
history, yes, that is, in my
историю да то есть получается в моём
case, I When God Tell me When God
случае я Когда Бог Вот скажи Когда Бог
chose When God said like you are the
избрал Когда Бог сказал типа что вы
chosen ones, we were probably the chosen ones
избранные мы избранные наверное были
when when we adopted Christianity
когда когда мы приняли христианство А
What is your God's name? Jesus Christ
как вашего Бога зовут Иисус Христос не
is not the son of God, but his
это сын Божий а его
father. Well, he is the Father, the son of this spirit. He has three
отца Ну он Отец сын сяй дух У него три
names. Well, this is the name of his father, what is the name of
им Ну вот имени у его отца как как зовут
Yahweh of the Sabans, we don't have that, we are not
Яхве савов не мы у нас нет такого мы не
Jews.
иудеи Подожди Стоп стоп стоп ты Библию
Whose only the New Testament The
чь только Новый Завет
New Testament is based on the
Новый Завет основывается на
World Cup in the New Testament there
ЧМ нуте в новом завете там же больше
were more prophets there are right Yes New
было пророков есть правильно Да ри Новый
Testament look let's look so good look like
Завет смотри давай так хорошо смотри
that God in the new testament and in the old
давай так Бог в новом завете и в старом
testament Is it the same God or
завете Это один и тот самый Бог или
some different ones
какие-то разные
gods This is one and the same God, one and the
боги Это один и тот же самый Бог один и
same God, yes, that is, it turns out that
самый Бог да то есть получается что у
you and the Jews have one and the same
вас и у евреев один и то самый
god. So come on,
бо Так давайте
come with us for your health
так давайте с нами за ваше здоровье
first. Oh, let’s give a godly deed to
сначала О давай богоугодное дело бухнуть
the Russian
русскому
nationalist, so look. I’m
националист так то смотри Вот мне
interested  here you have a God in the new testament and
интересно вот у вас Бог в новом завете и
in the old testament, they are the same, one and the
в старом завете это одинаковые один и
same God, not two different Gods. The truth. Well,
тот же Бог не два разных Бога Правда Ну
listen, well, damn it, you are an adult
слушайте Ну блин ну вы же взрослый
person and the same
человек один и тот самый
God. Well, an adult person already
Бог Ну у взрос человека уже сами
understands it themselves. That is, it turns out with Moses and
понимает То есть получается у Моисея и у
you have the same
вас один и тот же самый
God, you don’t understand, the Jews live according to the Old
Бог не понимаете евреи живут по ветхому
Testament, yes, yes, well, God, look, God, you,
завету да да нуно Бог у смотри Бог са Вы
but I understand correctly once again,
же са же са я правильно понимаю ещё раз
the God of Moses and you, the Russian
Бог у Моисея и у вас русского
nationalist, is the same,
националиста один и тот же самый Вы же
you are the same  I’m a Christian man, I’m not a believer, I’m
вы же человек христианин я не верующий Я
just studying religion, I’m a religion Vedas,
просто так изучаю религию я религия вед
you’re a theologian, yes, a theologian would be a theologian, yes,
вы теолог теолог Да теолог бы теолог Да
I graduated from seminary, like, but didn’t go, like
я заканчивал семинарию типа но не пошёл
Dasha, that is, see the question from Moses, from
Даше то есть смотрите вопрос У Моисея У
Abraham, and from you, by the way, what’s your name?
Авраама и у вас Вас кстати как зовут
My name is
Меня
Andrei Andre Very nice  they are changing the
Андрей Андре Очень приятно менят
city of Khmelnitsy I’m 42 years old, it turns out that
гр города хмельниц Мне 42 года
you have Herman from Moses, who
получается у вас Герман у Моисея который
led people in the desert for 40 years. Yes,
водил по пустыне 40 лет людей Да У
Abraham has the same God,
Авраама один и тот же самый Бог
right. Well, God, he has
правильно Ну Бог же он имеет
the same Christian theology. Well, you have the
жете христианской теологии Ну Бог у вас
same God. Well, let’s do it  look,
один и тот же самый Ну давай так смотри
you and Muslims have a different God, so
у вас и у мусульман разный Бог вот у
you have Allah or
тебя Аллах или
not No, I don’t believe in Allah is different
нет Нет я не верю в Аллаха разного Вот
You don’t believe, yes, but you believe in the
ты не веришь да но ты веришь в то в того
same god that Moses believed in
же бога что и верил в Моисей
True, well, Moses didn’t believe in God,
Правда Ну в Моисей не верил в Бога
Moses believed  in
Моисей Верил в
the prophet, let's say that Moses, who was the
пророка давай так у Моисея кто был
God of Yahweh Yahweh, is the same as
Богом Яхве Яхве так тот же самый что
well, the Jews believe that this is Jesus Christ
и ну иудеи считают что вот Иисус Христос
when there will be a Second Coming, that
когда Ну будет Второе пришествие что у
they will have their own God with Well, their Lord
них придёт свой Бог с Ну свой Господь
Mach Well, you understand more, but
Мах Ну вы вы больше разбирайтесь но тем
nevertheless, Well  For us, it will be the Antichrist
не менее Ну Для нас это будет антихрист
again, look, I’m not talking about
ещё раз смотри вот мне я сейчас не про
the prophets now, this is already like the second level, yes. So
пророков это уже типа второй уровень да
I’m looking at the top level. That
Вот я как по верхнему уровню смотрю То
is, you get God SN Jesus
есть у вас получается Бог СН Иисус
Christ God is the father of Yahweh,
Христос Бог отец Яхве
the same way it turns out He
так так же получается Он же послал
didn’t send his son  Jesus, too, is actually
своего сына не Иисус тоже на самом деле
one of the prophets, so and so, if so yes Well, that's
один из пророков так-то если вот так да
right But the father is the father What is the name of the
Ну правильно А вот отец отец Как имя
father the name of God who is the father of
отца имя Бога который отец
Jesus damn listen Well he's Yah he's
Иисуса блин слушайте Ну он же Ях он
chewing he's
жев он
the same and this is Open look in the new testament
же иу это Открой смотри в новом завете
Open and you how much  you will see the words of
Открой и ты сколько увидишь слов
Yahweh and I will see yes right yes, that is, look
Яхве и увижу да право да то есть смотри
it turns out that you are a Russian nationalist
получается что ты э русский националист
praying to the Jewish God I don’t pray to the
молишься еврейскому Богу я не молюсь
Jewish God you understand God he is One Yes
еврейскому Богу понимаете бог он Един Да
but for some reason he has the Jewish name Yahweh
но почему-то он с именем еврейским Яхве
and not for example there Ratibor Well damn Well
а не например там Ратибор Ну блин Ну тем
nevertheless  you know how, well, wait, wait, how,
не менее знаете как ну подожди подожди
nevertheless, look,
как тем не менее Вот смотри у славян
our Slavs had
наших де были
Russian
рус
SV, we are with you right now. You can also
СВ мы сечас с вами Вот вы можете тоже
talk about your topic there and support it. I just
разговаривать поддерживать Просто у меня
really have one moment. Well, that is, about
действительно один момен Ну то есть
well, exactly
Ну именно
religious religion,
религиозной религиозна ция
see  I don’t, I believe I believe that you believed Yes, I’m
см я ве не я верю верю что ты уверовал
just wondering, that is, it
Да мне просто интересно то есть ты
turns out you believed You’re a Russian
получается уверовал Ты русский
nationalist but you believe in the Jewish
националист но веришь в еврейского
national God Yes, I believe, believe
национального Бога Да я верю вери
the national God, may it be so for you Yes Yes, it’s
национального Бога пусть Вам Вам так
easier for me Yes, it’s
будет угодно Да Да мне так легче Да
interesting I love this  there among the Russian
интересно Я люблю вот это там у русских
nationalists This is such a discrepancy
националистов Вот это такое расхождение
interestingly understood Well listen Well damn he is the
интересно понял Ну слушайте Ну блин он
Lord he suffered for the sins of
он же Господь он же пострадал За грехи
all people Yes yes yes Absolutely true Yes
всех людей Да дада да Абсолютно верно Да
and he said that in short I sing for everyone People
и сказал что короче я пою за г всех Люде
I can even imagine now 2000 years
Я даже Представьте сейчас вот 2000 лет
have passed XX
прошло XX
century, damn it, I nevertheless feel
век блин я тем не менее чувствую в
in myself that I feel in order to so that well,
себе в себе что чувству с тем чтобы с
I am a sinful person, very
тем чтобы ну я я греховный человек очень
very bad And you just
очень плохой А ты вот это только что
drank this, this is what you
накатил это что ты
drank, what, well, you drank rooks, this is what
выпил что ну ты накатил грачиков это что
you drank, not not rooks  not me, I’m
ты бухнул не не грачиков не я вот я
just drinking tincture, tincture of
просто настоечка пью настоечка
what
чего
vodka I’m just this on Instagram Just
водки Я просто это Инстаграме Просто
tincture Pi Orthodox
настоечка Пи православненько
Orthodox for Jesus no what something what
православненько за Иисуса нет то что то
no what Ukraine has lost the Lord
что нет то что Украина лишилась Господа
that Ukraine has followed the satanic path
то что Украина пошла по сатанинском пути
this is a fact that Ukraine will not not
это факт то что Украина не не будет
exist this too  fact yes But
существовать это тоже факт да А вот
look, okay, let’s do this Russia is an
смотри хорошо давай так Россия - это
Orthodox country yes Yes Ukraine is
православная страна да Да Украина - это
Orthodox And well uh Ramzan Kadyrov is an
православная А хорошо э Рамзан Кадыров
Orthodox person Ramzan Kadyrov is not
православный человек Рамзан Кадыров не
an Orthodox person Wait, how do
православный человек Подождите а как у
you get non-Orthodox orders in an Orthodox country?
вас в православной стране получается не
We don’t have a
православные порядки не у нас
multinational state Yes, I understand
многонациональная государство Да понял
that is, your state is not Orthodox.
то есть у вас не православное значит
Well, most Russian people,
государство Ну большинство русских людей
of course, Russian people always count. That is,
конечно русские люди всегда счи То есть
I
я правильно
understand correctly that you 197 Wait, wait, in
понима что вы 197 Подожди подожди вы в
1917 you refused to shoot the
1917 году отказались расстреляли
Orthodox
православного
Tsar, you renounced the
царя отреклись от веры
Orthodox faith, you left the churches, churches.
православной поскидали храмы церкви У
I just understand like, well, here  as
меня просто понимаете типа ну у нас как
if we have a chat here we
бы вот у нас есть вот чат у нас вот люди
have people fighting for Ukraine Lord for Well
есть воюют за за Украину Господи за Ну
reservist sa Hala for
резервист са Хала за
Israel we support Israel who are
Израиль мы поддерживаем Израиль кто
you Well I am my own I am my friends and so on
вы Ну я свои я свои друже и так далее
My father
Мой отец
Supports we just have a friend there
Поддерживает у нас там просто есть друг
we are for  Well, we seem to be for him. How can we
мы за Ну мы как бы за него Как мы можем
support someone who is not our own? Well, there are others who have
поддерживать не своего Ну там други есть
their own friends, I understand, in short, you are a
свои друзья понял то ты короче ты
Russian nationalist, you support
русский националист поддерживаешь
Israel now,
Израиль сейчас
of course, and Putin supports Hamas.
так конечно а Путин поддерживает Хамас
Yes, Putin does not support anyone. Hamas.
Да Путин никого не поддерживает Хамас
Where did you see this? And Putin is a Russian
Где вы такого увидели а Путин он русский
nationalist or  not
националист или не
Russian Putin is a multinational
русский Путин многонациональный
nationalist understood multinational on
националист понял многонациональный на
No matter how
Как бы как бы то ни было не звучало
strange it may sound Putin himself said
странно Путин сам сказал
multinational nation You understand I
многонациональная нация Сами понимаете
understand this is a kind of dialectic Yes I
Поня это такая диалектика Да как вот это
don’t understand this you think we ourselves understand
я не понимаю вы думаете мы сами понимаем
what kind of dialectic Well look if you
что за диалектика Ну смотри е если ты
understand  that God 31n then why couldn’t you
понял что бог 31н то почему ты не мог
understand that the Russian nation is
понять что русская нация
multinational No, well, damn Russian
многонациональна Не ну ну блин русские
people
люди
NN I understood Russian
НН я понял россиянин
Well, you know, Russians are also different,
Ну знаете россияне тоже разные бывают
different, I
разные
understood But this is what you Russian
понял А вот чем Вот вы русские
nationalists do besides roulette,
националисты занимаетесь кроме рулетки
here we support the Russian national
вот мы поддерживаем русскую национальную
idea in
идею в
the boundary
межи
Well  you know, Russian Russian community Call, you can
Ну знаете рус русская община Зов можете
subscribe, in fact, we are against
подписаться на самом деле мы против
ethnic lawlessness, ethnic bans,
этнического беспредела этнических бан
wait, well, in Russia we have a
подожди ну у нас есть в России есть
problem that is very huge, very loud, look,
проблема очень огро очень ором смотри
besides the telegram, you have some kind of
кроме телеграма у вас какая-то
activity, of course I’m
деятельность есть конечно я Я же вам
telling you, like we have it
говорю типа он у нас
very  a big problem in terms of migration
очень большая проблема в плане миграции
in terms of ethnic gangs is that people I
в плане этнических Банд то что люди Я
know what migration for example interrupt You
знаю чём миграци например перебивайте Вы
interrupt a lot Tell Tell
очень много перебивать Раскажи Расскажи
me it’s always interesting Dada Tell me well, we have we
мне интересно постоянно Дада Расскажи ну
have a group on telegram
у нас есть у нас есть группа в телеграме
Russian community Call Ugu
русская община Зов Угу
z Well, you understand
з Ну вы поняли
y Well, listen  in our country, you know, in
у Ну слушайте у нас в стране понимаете У
our country it is promoted, that is, not just, well,
нас в стране пропагандируется то есть не
Friendship of Peoples, but some
то что ну Дружба народов но какая-то
kind of well, that is, we also have
некая ну то есть у нас тоже есть
uncontrolled migration, definitely
бесконтрольная миграция определённо
speaking, because employees and different
говоря потому что сотрудники и разные
people really, well, let people through
люди действительно Ну пропускают людей
who even deport people back, well
которые даже людей депортируют обратно
people from Russia are returning back to us, there are people who are inadequate in general, that is, they
люди есть неадекватные вообще то есть
form their own Well, ethnic
составляют свои Ну этнические
groups How old are you by the way 22
группировки А тебе сколько лет кстати 22
22 How many children do you have zero and how many
22 Сколько у тебя детей ноль а сколько у
children does an ethnic migrant have at 22
этнического мигранта детей в 22
years old I don’t keep track of them
года я за ними не слежу
but at least you have a girlfriend there  Russian,
а девушка у тебя хоть есть там русская
some kind of Ukrainian Well, like Slavyanka
какая-то Украинки Ну типа Славянка
Slavyanka what was Slavyanka is there is
Славянка что было Славянка есть есть
Slavyanka Yes, it’s always as
Славянка Да меня всегда вот как как как
if I didn’t have it I was drawn to me I
будто не было у меня тянуло у меня
have a girl from Kiev I know, a very
девчонка есть из Киева знакомая очень
kind girl from Kiev Well, we talked with her
добрая девчонка из Киева Ну мы с ней
here, let’s say in Moscow  Well,
общались здесь скажем так в Москве Ну
she’s there, well, she’s very not, she’s very pro
она там ну она очень не она очень про
Ukrainian girl, like, but damn, she’s cool,
украинская девчонка типа но блин крутая
really cool, and there’s a girl who’s
реально крутая и есть девчонка которая
pro Ukrainian, here she’s right here, damn, this
про украинская здесь она прямо вот вот
happens to me all the time.
блин вот постоянно у меня так бывает Угу
Your parents are also Russian. As I
тебя родители же тоже русские Я так
understand it, they were. Well, my parents, my mother
понимаю были Ну у меня родители у меня
was born in Rostov. Danu’s father is in the
мат родилась в Ростове Дану отец в
Krasnodar Territory, yes. And why did they
Краснодарском крае да А с чего они тебя
name you Germa
с перепуга назвали Герма
Ani there elam
Ани там елам
Ioan, out of fear, I don’t know honestly, I
Иоан не знаю честно исконно русскими
can’t
именами не могу
say with native Russian names well, but  for example, is
сказать хорошо а вот например
your last name Russian or not Russian? It’s a
твоя фамилия она русская или не русская
shamraev surname, yes. It’s clearly not
Вот она шамраев фамилия да Это явно не
Russian, you see, the
русская понимаете там
problem is that all the surnames are Chechen, they were
проблема все фамилии чеченские они
originally Russified, well, wait,
русифицирован изначально ну подожди ну
sri shamraev. This is most likely on behalf of
сри шамраев Это скорее всего от имени
some kind of Turkic shamrai. No. In
тюркского какого-то шамрай нет На самом
fact, if we google  shamray shamray
деле если мы будем гуглить шамрай шамрай
Yes, you're right, in fact,
Да вы право на самом деле тоже Татарская
there is a Tatar one too. Well, part of it. And if there is such a name,
есть Ну часть А если есть такое имя
more accurately, the word shamray is a Ukrainian
точнее слово шамрай - это украинское
word. Although it would seem that there is such a
слово Хотя Казалось бы о Есть такая
village as shamraevka near the Kiev region,
деревня шамраевка под Киевской областью
from the White Church, I’m really Yes, there
вот от белай церкви я вот реально Да
is a shamray in Polish Ukrainian
есть в польском украинском есть шамрай
Yes, you got away with it, you're lucky, yeah, but
да отмазался ты тебе повезло яму Да но
look, if you were Polish,
смотри если бы ты был польский
Ukrainian, you were either shamray or
украинский ты был или бы шамрай ский или
or shamray, I don't have me, I have
или шамрай не у меня у меня у меня у
a lot of Poles, in fact, there
меня много Поляков на самом деле тоже
are also further Oh, you're already We'll Russify you a little
есть далее О ты уже Мы тебя немножко
already You  I’m not quite
русифицировать уже Ты уже не совсем
Russian anymore I’m a Russian person, well, somehow
русский Я русский человек да ну как-то
we’ve already found the Poles Well,
уже и Поляков мы нашли
listen, Nunu, many Russians have
Ну слушайте нуну у многих русских есть
Poles, actually I understand, yes Well, it’s a
поляки на самом деле понял да А ну так
very intimate question, but there are no Jews in my family
очень интимный вопрос а евреев в роду
and I do
нету нету а
n’t know any Germans Well, you don’t
немцев не знаю Ну как не
know  Chen
знае Чен в
is not in the Rada. Well, I just know there, well, great-grandfathers, great-grandmothers,
нет Вот я просто знаю там ну прадедушек
so on, yes, okay, but
прабабушек так далее понял да хорошо а
look, I understand correctly that
вот смотри я правильно что понимаю что
you are a representative of a subculture there or
ты представитель ээ субкультуры там или
like a movement Yes, which held
как движения Да которое проводило
Russian
русские
marches ru Russian marches Russian marches have been gone for a
марши ру русских маршев русских маршев
long, long time Yes, well  you
уже давно-давно нет Да ну вы же
carried it out, well, your Russian
проводили это ж Ваши русские
nationalists or
националисты или
not, you understand it was carried out by the Russian Mash
нет понимаете проводил русский Маш
Dmitry Dyomushkin Dyomushkin Potkin, in short,
Дмитрий дёмушкин дёмушкин поткин короче
everyone carried it out there, yes, that is, Dmitry
там все проводили да то есть Дмитрий
Dyomushkin is an absolutely pro-UK
дёмушкин - это абсолютно проу нский
Dude now he’s yes yes He’s talking about the Ukrainian
Чувак сейчас он да да Он про украинский
Absolutely right about the Ukrainian Well, let’s just
Абсолютно верно про украинский Да ну
say he’s not  he is so pro-unsky, he is
скажем так он не столько проу нский он
anti-war, like he says that this is a damn
антивоенный типа он говорит что это блин
war, he he clearly says that this War
война он он Чётко говорит что эта Война
is harmful to the Russian nation,
идёт на вред русской нации
Dmit Demushkin is a traitor and an enemy, a
дмит демушкин это предатель и враг
traitor
предатель
to the Russians. And what is he saying that’s so bad, that’s
кого русских А что он такого плохого
interesting, I read Yoshkin and
говорит вот интересно я читал ёшкина и
watched his show.  he says this
смотрел его переда что он говорит такого
against the Russians Dmitry Dyomushkin
против русских Дмитрий дёмушкин
absolutely Because if
абсолютно Потому что если рос если
Russia loses Donbass, if Russia
Россия потеряет Донбасс если Россия
loses all the
потеряет все захваченные скажем так
territories it has captured, let’s say, then this means the loss of
территории то это означает потерю
Russian identity, this means the collapse of
русской идентичности это означает развал
Russia,
России
as a Ukrainian nationalist, you
как украинский националист вс-таки тоже
should also understand that Russia will grow up. Let’s say
должны понимать что рос
you too  Russian nationalists What can you do in
и вы русские националисты Что можете в
Russia, you are ruled by Chechens, in short, by
России у вас правят чеченцы короче кто
anyone Yes, but not you, no one
угодно Да но не вы не у нас никто не
rules here, why look, for example,
правит у нас почему смотри например вот
this guy you know Nikita Zhuravel,
этот парень знаешь Никита Журавель
whom Kadyrov’s son drank in the SZ I
которого сын Кадырова отпил в сзо
know very well Yes, and that some of you
прекрасно знаю Да и что кто-то из вас
defended Nikita the crane even in a telegram
защитил Никиту журавля хоть в телеграме
yes se How we
да се Как
fully defended him we fully
защитили полностью мы по полностью е
support him well support him they are kicking him
поддерживаем ну поддержите его пиздят по
action action action sad like well you
него поступок поступок поступок
can’t
печальный типа ну нельзя нельзя так
do that Yes you can’t do it like he did
сделать Да нельзя сделать он типа сделал
there yes yes there
там
is The law is the law yes According to what
ду да есть Закон есть закон да По какому
law is it  they took it, they gave it away, it wasn’t work according to
закону его взяли отдали не работа по
some kind of method, definitely in Chechnya, they
методически какой-то определённо в Чечню
took the answer to the camera from just so
забрали отве во на камеру от просто так
hard Yes, they also gave an order to
что жесть Да вот ещё эти дали орден
this little Kadyrov Yes, for the fact that he
малому этому Кадырову Да за то что он
beat the first Russian at the age of 15 and that’s
первого русского побил в 15 лет и вот и
what you are Russian nationalists for  they
что вы русские националисты по всей
did it all over Russia, so you’re just
России сделали вот вот вы просто
saying section,
говорите разд
don’t just tell me how you, as a Russian
не просто вот скажи как ты как русский
nationalist, supported Nikita
националист поддержал Никиту
Zhuravel Well, wait Nikita
журавля Ну подождите Никита
Zhuravel Zhuravel You’re also reading
Журавель Журавель Вы тоже читаете
Parker, it turns out Ale Paquet I’m still reading, I have
паркера получается Але Паке Я всё читаю
this kind of being kind, we all
у меня такая быть добру мы все
respect being kind, I understand, listen Well
уважаем быть добру я понял слушайте Ну
Damn, we don’t support this, well,
блин мы не поддерживаем это да ну
wait, you didn’t protect him, they beat him
подождите вы его не защитили его бьют
while on camera, as a Chechen
это пока на камеру как чеченец
mocks a Russian, Kadyrov’s son,
издевается над русским сын Кадырова
a minor, beats a Russian guy like
малолетний избивает русского парня как
damn, like some kind of carcass, and what did you do?
блин как тушу какую-то и что вы сделали
No, he knocks him down, too, like a carcass.
Не ну он сбивает тоже как тушу Там че
the person is powerless, like obviously, and
просто человек бессилен типа очевидно и
also knocks down the same question. How he beats,
тоже сбивает тоже вопрос Как избивает
beats from the knee, in short, a pancake from the butt,
избивает с колена короче блин с приклада
you
Ты же
saw Yes, and especially We saw how
видел Да и особенно Мы видели как сын
Kadyrov’s son also participated later, yes, like with
Кадырова в также участ потом да типа с
not then not then before that, he also
не потом не потом до этого тоже
participated again, look at your
участвовал ещё раз смотри вот вашего
Russian  the guy, maybe he did something
русского парня может он сделал что-то
wrong, the Chechens took him to a pre-trial detention center and
неправильно чеченцы забрали в СИЗО и
just beat him up like a toy and show
просто как игрушку лупят и показывают
that they are
что они
little mermaids
русачок
please how does this affect
пожалуйста как это влияет
the bombing of Ukraine and
на бомбардировка Украины причём
the bombing of Ukraine I’m telling you what
бомбардировка Украины Я говорю что
you say
вым вы говорите
in the Russian Federation it affects How
в Российской Федерации это влияет Как
it
это
affects Why you are interested Because  that you are a
влияет Почему вы интересе Потому что ты
Russian nationalist Yes, how are you? You are
русский националист Да как ты себя Ты
nobody in Russia, in short, tomorrow Ramzan
никто в России тебя короче завтра Рамзан
Kadyrov will say Shut up your hawala,
Кадыров скажет Заткни своё хавало
the information field will not happen, and the
информационное поле такого не будет а
information field is as good as your
информационное поле так хорошо как ваше
information field helped Nikita ZhV
информационное поле помогло Никите жв
so that his son is not a star, the son of Ramzan
чтобы его не звезд сын Рамзана
Kadyrov,
Кадырова
this is chaos, you and I  we don’t argue as
это беспредел мы с вами не спорим так
correctly as you prevent this
правильно как вы препятствует этому
lawlessness, how you cheated, went to the
беспределу как вы изменили вышли на
rally, said Kadyrov is a dog, get out of
митинг сказали Кадыров пёс шал вон с
our Earth, let go of our Russian, what
нашей Земли Отпусти нашего русского что
did you do or cry in the telegram, I
вы сделали или поплакали в телеграме я с
don’t argue with you, I don’t argue with you, Well, that
тобой не спорю я с тобой не спорю Ну то
is, you admit that you  all the Russian
есть ты признаёшь что вы все российские
nationalists who are now
националисты которые вот сейчас мы
bombing Ukraine, you are Prima All of you can’t
бомбим Украину вы Прима Всё вы не можете
protect one Russian guy in Russia,
защитить одного русского парня в России
but it turns out
да получается
like this Live now Sati Slava well
ка Живи теперь Сати Слава ну
Live Glory to
Живите Слава
Ukraine kiny damage It’s just a [ __ ] up
Украине кины ущерб Просто капец
fuck-fly
бляха-муха
Russian [ __ ] nationalist nabhi
русский бля националист набхи
we are here we are leading this Russian  in
мы тут мы ведём русскую эту в
[laughs]
[смех]
telegram So they give you stars not in
телеграме Так звездюлей вам дают не в
telegram but on
телеграме а в
Instagram
Инстаграме
Damn face at the end she’s just
Б льно лицо в конце она просто
like that Well, it turns out that’s how she
тако Ну да получается
sits. They’re really sitting there, so
так сидит Вот они там реально сидят
downcast, just powerless, and
такие опущенные просто да бесправные да
they’re just being mocked; they’re being driven out by the
над ними просто издеваются уже гонят
Kadyrovs just like dogs  thinks Yes, he
Кадыров просто их как собак считает Да
laughs at them like yes And this one we are there about
смеётся с них типа да А этот мы там ро
you You are there chuk You’re just You’re pathetic
вас Т вы там чук Ты просто Ты жалкий
pathetic you just know I don’t know if there are
жалкий просто знаешь вот я не знаю есть
any they meet They at least
какие-то встречаются Они хоть какую-то
have some kind of pride there damn how you
имеют там гордость блин как нужно себя
don’t have to respect yourself It’s just crap  I have no
не уважать Просто капец это у меня нет
words subscribe to the channel Yes Like it,
слов подпишитесь на канал Да Поставьте
leave a comment what do you think about
лайк залиште комент что вы думаете про
this video Glory to Ukraine write to my
це видео Слава Украине пись на мий
Telegram directly at once axis of wine and
Telegram прям зараз ось вин а
popk more and more respectfully YouTube borrowing
попк це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through skarg or in your ban and I
нас через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже
don’t show much more video  People are constantly not
багато видео не показую людям вчасно не
showing information about the stream. To that end,
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
we need to write a Mali operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
right away and Popik is there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
Telegra okm video sche tezh Tsikava and
телегра окм видео ще теж цикава и
Korisna information and we are guilty of you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
trima postiyny operational link
трима постийний оперативный звязок
independantly in that
незалежно в того
chi show you about it YouTube Slava
чи покаже вам про це YouTube Слава
Write to Ukraine
пиши